LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Aramaki-San, my sincere apologies
for making you come all the way here.
Now that Undersecretary of Foreign Affairs
Kim has received an assassination threat,
the situation falls under our jurisdiction.
Moreover, you graciously provided us with
critical information in an earlier matter.
The Undersecretary has arrived
in Kagoshima on schedule.
We have waited for five long years.
Undersecretary Kim is the first high-profile government
official to pay a visit to honour war casualties
after permission was granted to do so.
Aramaki-San, I ask that you provide
the best possible protection.
Understood.
Then I will leave it in your hands.
Batou, you have temporary command here.
What?! You have a personal errand
at an important time like this?
I'll be back by nightfall.
Saitou, Pazu, and Bomer, stay with Batou.
Coordinate closely with the Major
as she tries to track down who made the threat.
So, where are you going?
To pay my respects to a friend on the
seventh anniversary of his funeral.
Assassination
Duet
You're late.
Just before you arrived, many of Tsujisaki's
acquaintances paid their respects.
Is that so? I'm sorry.
Effective treatment for cyberbrain
scleroses did not exist back then.
Tsujisaki Clan
Those who will be sorely missed
tend to pass away earlier.
True. Of the three of us, Tsujisaki was the
one who was most favoured by Colonel Tonoda.
I know how you feel about the Colonel.
I only did as the Colonel ordered.
That's just like you.
Ah, yes.
Understood.
I'll return immediately.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
That's fine.
If I remember correctly, you are Tsujisaki's...
Yes, I'm Saori.
I'm sure that my father is glad
to have you here, Aramaki-San.
He said that you helped him in many
ways during my mother's funeral rites.
You were still a student back then.
I believe you also had a younger brother
in elementary school, didn't you?
Yes.
Um... There's something I'd like to ask you about.
And that is?
It's about my brother, Yuu.
He has suddenly begun acting like my father.
He was raised well.
He resembles Tsujisaki, when he was young.
No, that's not what I mean.
It's not just a physical resemblance.
Both his voice and manner of speech
are now quite similar to our father's.
Does that pose some kind of problem?
He recently began to access military news sites,
though he has never shown any interest before now.
In addition, I sometimes wake up in the night
because I hear a noise in the living room.
and I find my brother sitting there
reading my father's books very intently.
I don't even know when he sleeps,
since this has been occurring nightly.
Now that you mention it,
I could never tell when Tsujisaki slept, either.
Yes. When I became worried and
asked him what he was doing,
all he did was to look at me and
ask, "Saori, you're still awake?"
That's not all.
It seems like he is contacting
someone a lot lately.
But he won't tell me who,
no matter how many times I ask him.
Large packages from overseas keep arriving too...
Do you think it's possible that he
might be involved in something strange?
Please, I want you to investigate
why he changed so suddenly.
I'm very sorry, but I cannot use my professional
authority for private matters like this.
You may confide in me, but I cannot help
you based on what you have told me so far.
That's true, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I heard that you were a good friend
of my father's, so I thought...
Tsujisaki was not a friend,
he was just a comrade-in-arms.
I know.
Yes, I'll do it.
I'll do it right, okay?
I know...
Chinese Undersecretary of Foreign
Affairs, Kim, arrived today.
He plans to pay homage to
Kagoshima's war casualties tomorrow.
Since many Chinese who were
living in Okinawa at the time
were interred in the memorial
monolith alongside the Japanese,
the Chinese government has expressed
its desire to pay an official visit.
The Japanese government issued special
permission for this particular visit;
the culmination of this is
Undersecretary Kim's visit to Japan.
In addition, the police appear to have heightened security
measures in place due to increased protests by the Japanese.
The Old Man is purposefully
letting himself be seen on TV.
How easygoing of him...
An here we are laying low,
toiling away in our pursuit of the suspect...
Any clues as to the target's identity?
Hmm, well... This just came in.
This is the assassin who is
targeting Undersecretary Kim?
After analysing the Undersecretary's schedule,
we reached the conclusion that the
assassin would probably be a sniper.
Using that assumption to narrow
down our list of suspects,
we found evidence that a
sophisticated sniper rifle had been
carefully disassembled and shipped in
as separate parts via the Etorofu route.
From there, we determined the
addressee of the packages,
and the individual who came to pick up the packages that
had been sent to P.O. boxes at different locations...
is that person there.
I'm having the system run an
identity check using this image,
but it will take about two more
hours for the results to come back.
Have you determined the identity of the suspect?
We haven't reached a final conclusion,
but judging from the circumstances,
he is our best candidate.
Someone you know?
Tsujisaki Yuu, son of the former chief of
GSDF Intelligence, Colonel Tsujisaki Hideo,
I told you, I'll do it.
I know.
Kim, the Undersecretary of Foreign
Affairs, Will Visit the Memorial Monument
I have to do it.
It's to avenge my mother's...
Ritsuko's death, after all.
Isn't that right, Yuu?
Stay quiet.
Major, we missed him.
He already left.
I'm sorry to visit at this ungodly hour.
Ishikawa, he knew we were coming.
Run a check on all transportation
monitors immediately.
Understood.
Y-You are...?
I work under Aramaki.
Under Aramaki-San...?
Yes.
To get straight to the point,
we came here to detain your
brother, Tsujisaki Yuu.
Detain... Detain Yuu?
He already left the premises.
At least knock, will you?
This is the room of a lady.
Sorry.
Major, I found this on his desk.
What has Yuu done?
You know of Undersecretary of Foreign Affairs,
Kim, who is currently visiting Japan, don't you?
There has been a threat against his life,
and your brother is the number one suspect.
That can't be...
While we don't know his motives, we have confirmed that
he has hacked into Colonel Tsujisaki's SDF data library.
The records indicate that he accessed it starting
on the day after his birthday until yesterday.
The reason why his intrusion
went undetected until now
is that he opened the maintenance
firewall using the proper "keys".
Yuu did such things...?
How long has your brother been
using the portable terminal?
Yuu received a package containing the portable
terminal our father used on his sixteenth birthday.
When Yuu was little, it perplexed my
father that Yuu really wanted the terminal.
At the time, my father promised Yuu that
he'd give him the terminal when Yuu grew up.
The password for the maintenance firewall
must have been stored in the terminal.
We are trying to access the library ourselves,
but cracking the password is proving
difficult and will require several hours.
At this point, only your
brother knows what is in there.
He has been fascinated with
it since it was delivered.
He won't tell me anything...
In any case, I wonder where
he is at this time of night...
Considering that he is no longer here,
we should assume that he has entered
the final stages of the assassination.
Please stop my brother!
Please don't let him become a murderer!
That's why we're here.
Major.
Did you find something?
There is no sign of him on the monitors
at train stations and airports at present.
However, something about
Colonel Tsujisaki caught my eye.
Something about Colonel Tsujisaki?
It's something I heard while I was
still working with the military.
Our Chief, the current Chief of
GSDF Intelligence, Kubota and
Colonel Tsujisaki used to be called
"The Three Crows of the Tonoda School."
In particular, Colonel Tsujisaki was respected by his peers,
and his course for new members received special accolades.
From sharpshooting to disarming explosives,
hand-to-hand combat,
weapons acquisition and even covert ops...
It is said that he thought a wide range of
skills was important and cultivated many experts.
From here on, it is only speculation on my part,
but consider Tsujisaki Yuu's action thus far and the degree
of cunning in his apparent ability to predict our movements.
If you put the two together...
His father's library was a collection of war
tactics that had been accumulated over the years,
and Tsujisaki Yuu succeeded in secretly obtaining that
information by using the password in his father's terminal.
In other words, his mind is now that of an assassin who has
been trained by an extremely capable intelligence officer?
I do not have conclusive proof,
but considering how he was continued to brilliantly
circumvent all efforts on our part to capture him,
the possibility is high.
Batou, don't let the fact that he is the son of
my old friend affect your operation.
Protecting Undersecretary
Kim is our foremost priority.
Don't think about anything else.
It's not as if I didn't intend to do just
that from the beginning, of course...
Chief, that may be true,
but I will try to spare his life anyway.
However, in the worst-case scenario...
Of course.
Chief Aramaki, there is a message from
the GSDF with encryption code 839-0852.
It's an old GSDF encryption code.
Decode and route it to me.
It has been a long time
since we last spoke, Aramaki.
Tsujisaki...?
What is this about?
At first, I had no intention of doing anything.
I just wanted to tell "myself" the truth...
The truth that I would want
passed on to posterity.
In order to do that,
I overwrote my memory onto my son's cyberbrain.
I never thought that would
make me into an assassin.
What did you hide in the data library?
The truth behind the Okinawa Incident.
I just wanted that truth to
be passed on to posterity.
But upon learning the truth,
"I" learned the truth behind my mother's death,
and that only created a desire for vengeance.
This is unexpected.
I did not even think once about assassination.
But I am no longer able to
stop "my" desire for vengeance.
Vengeance, after all these years?
That's not like you.
I agree.
But now, I'm Tsujisaki Hideo and
Tsujisaki Yuu at the same time.
Mingled memories now flow together in our consciousness,
and "I" act on my thoughts.
Or, is it the opposite?
When this is finished, it may be that I
will become someone entirely different.
Do you intend to make your son into an assassin?
If it could at all help it, I would prefer not to.
But you know what? No one can stop this.
It must be Yuu's youth that necessitates this.
Take care of Saori for me.
It seems that I must have my vengeance.
Tsujisaki...!
I'm sorry, Aramaki.
Damn it, we can't even catch him using ID codes.
Can't we just prevent general visitors
from entering the grounds?
Undersecretary Kim requested permission to have as many
associates with him as possible to console the deceased.
So, he's basically asking to be killed.
No matter the outcome,
it'll be a great performance, I guess.
Saitou, can you scope out possible sniping points?
He has a sniper rifle with
an extremely long range.
Even if he has disassembled it for
portability, it should still be quite obvious.
If he's planning to make the kill as a sniper,
my current location is the best position.
Other locations suffer from a
strong sea breeze and obstructions.
He would not be able to shoot with any accuracy.
Heh, fishing in a time like this?
Bomer.
Yeah?
Nothing here, either.
According to the programme,
the presentation of flowers is next.
It's the best opportunity, since the SP
will have to step away from his side.
Where is he?!
Where is he targeting from?
We've found the weapon!
What about the sniper?
There's no sign of him.
All we've found is one sniper rifle
and a student whose uniform was taken.
So, the rifle was a ruse!
Major, I didn't know that you were here.
We were able to determine the
actual plot from Tsujisaki's data.
According to him,
"The most effective assassination method is to approach
the target without regard for an escape route."
An assassin with a one-way ticket, huh?
What?!
Undersecretary Kim safely completed all of his
planned events and departed yesterday afternoon.
It was a risky operation,
but we could see no option other than to implant a
memory that he succeeded in his quest for vengeance.
Unfortunately, he may not remember
you even if he regains consciousness.
It is quite possible that he is now a stranger
who is neither your brother nor your father.
It does not matter...
as long as Yuu lives and stays by my side.
If anything happens, contact this number.
Thank you.
Using the data that the father left behind,
the son reconstructed the father's memories and
attempted to have the two personalities coexist.
As a result, each personality affected the other.
However, I think that the procedure
erased Colonel Tsujisaki's memories.
In addition, while the possibility is remote,
it is possible that he'll return to
being the boy named Tsujisaki Yuu.
True.
However, it is rather trying to lose
a close friend twice in my old age.
I thought he was your comrade-in-arms.
You're right.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up